Guide to the Charles W. Poletti Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XIII: Clipping Books, 1933-1948
  - Clippings Scrapbook, 1939 (Box 68)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, 1940 (Box 69)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, 1941 (Box 70)
  - Clippings Scrapbook, 1941-1942 (Box 71)
  - Scrapbook, 1947-1948 (Box 72)